Guide to the Administrative Papers of Chancellor George Bugliarello RG.007
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series III: Publications and Manuscripts, 4342
  - Subseries B: Publication Original Copies, 3542
    - Publications – Original Copies- 18-39, 1962-1966; 3544 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Publications – Original Copies – 40-59, 1966-1971; 3545 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Publications – Original Copies- 60-77, 1969-1970; 3546 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Publications – Original Copies- 78-94, 1969-1970; 3547 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Publications – Original Copies- 95-106, 1971-1972; 3548 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Publications – Original Copies- 107-124, 1973-1975; 3549 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Publications – Original Copies- 125-145, 1975-1980; 3550 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Publications – Original Copies- 146-160, 1980-1984; 3551 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Publications – Original Copies- 161-177, 1984; 3552 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Publications – Original Copies – 178 – 189, 1986-1987; 3553 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Publications – Original Copies – 190 – 216, 1987-1991; 3554 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Publications – Original Copies – 217 – 235, 1991-1995; 3555 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Publications – Original Copies – 236- 259, 1994-1999; 3556 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Publications – Original Copies – 260-284, 1999-2003; 3557 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Publications – Original Copies – 285-306, 2003-2007; 3558 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Publications – Original Copies – 307-327, 2007-2011; 3559 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Subseries C: Manuscripts, 3111
    - Socio-Technology – Binder #1 – 1, Undated; 3112 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Socio-Technology – Binder #1 – 2, Undated; 3113 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Socio-Technology – Binder #1 – 3, Undated; 3114 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - George Bugliarello Membership – Binder # 1 – 1, Undated; 3115 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - George Bugliarello Membership – Binder # 1 – 2, Undated; 3116 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - George Bugliarello Membership – Binder # 1 – 3, Undated; 3117 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - George Bugliarello Membership – Binder # 1 – 4, Undated; 3118 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Socio-Technology – Binder #2 – 1, 2001; 3119 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Socio-Technology – Binder #2 – 2, 2001; 3120 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Technology & Merchandising - Binder #1 - 1, 2001; 5587 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Technology & Merchandising - Binder #1 - 2, 2001; 5588 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Photocopies of Business cards, Undated; 3121 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - "Computers and Water Resources" – Part 1, Undated; 3122 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - "Computers and Water Resources" – Part 2, Undated; 3123 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Publication Compilation - 1, Undated; 5551 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Publication Compilation - 2, Undated; 5552 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Publication Compilation - 3, Undated; 5553 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Publication Compilation - 4, Undated; 5554 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Publication Compilation - 5, Undated; 5555 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Publication Compilation - 6, Undated; 5556 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Subseries D: Biosoma, 2902
    Biosoma, a term coined by George Bugliarello, refers to the interaction between biology, society and machines. This subseries contains manuscripts, publications, drafts, notes, and research materials relating to George Bugliarello's research and promotion of the Biosoma paradigm.
    - Article - "Biology, Machines and Society: Designing the Future of Our Species" Presentation – Transparencies, Undated; 2917 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Article - "Biosoma Engineering" – Drafts, 2010 December- 2011 January; 2910 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Article - "The Biosoma Paradigm for Earth Systems Engineering", 2004 March - 2005 November; 2911 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Article - "The Biosoma Paradigm and Environmental Engineering" – Proofs, Published Copy, 2007 January, March; 2909 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Article - "The Biosoma Paradigm and Environmental Engineering" – Submission, 2004 September - 2007 May; 2921 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Article - "The Biosoma: The Symbiosis of Man, Society and Machine", 1979; 5529 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Article - "The Biosoma: The Symbiosis of Man, Society and Machine" – Draft, 1982; 5530 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Article - "The Biosoma: The Synthesis of Biology, Machines, and Society" – Edits – Bulletin of Science, Technology & Society, 2000 December; 2922 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Article - "For a Human Future: Reflections on the Synthesis of Biology, Society and Machines (The Biosoma)", 2000; 5531 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Article - "Reflections on Machines and the Synthesis of Biological Organisms, Society and Machines" – Revised Texts, 1999 November 11; 5532 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Article - "Reflections on Machines" – Drafts, 1996-1997; 2926 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Article - "Reflections on Machines" – Presentations, Undated; 2927 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Biosoma Design, 2010-2012; 5533 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Book Mailings, 2003 April - 2005 June; 2903 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Draft – "June 20 Version", Undated; 5534 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Drafts, Undated; 2908 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Drafts, Transparencies, 1998 September; 2918 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Figures, Undated; 2913 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Final Publication, 2003; 2904 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Franz J. Gayl, 2005 February; 2915 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Harmony Books Publisher, 1998; 5535 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Internet Submission, 1999 June - 2000 July; 5536 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Internet Submission, 2000 October - 2005 April; 5537 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Machine Figures – Revisions, 1997 January 21; 2929 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Manuscript, 1988; 2906 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Manuscript – 1, 1999 August; 2919 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Manuscript – 2, 1999 August; 2920 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Manuscript - "Engineering for a Better Human Future: Reflections on the Synthesis of Biology, Society and Machines (The Biosoma)" - 2000, 3740 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Manuscript - "For a Human Future: Reflections on the Synthesis of Biology, Society and Machines (The Biosoma)", 2000; 5581 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous, 1999 September - 2004 July; 5538 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 2005 April-June, Undated; 5539 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous – Manuscript Drafts, 1988-1989, Undated; 2924 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous – Manuscript Drafts - Notes, Undated; 2923 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous - Presentations, Copies, Undated; 5540 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous – Presentations, 1996, Undated; 5541 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - New Graphics, 1998 February, 1999 June-July; 2914 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Outlines & Notes, Undated; 5542 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Presentation – Long Version, 1998 September 4; 2916 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Presentation copies & transparencies – "Designing the Future of our Species", Undated; 5543 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Presentations, 1996 April; 2905 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Principles of Biosoma Design, 2010 December 9; 5544 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Reviews & Reviewer Correspondence, 1979 May - 1988 November; 2907 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Revision – Terry Bristol – 1, 1999 August; 5545 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Revision – Terry Bristol – 2, 1999 August; 5546 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - The New Press, 2001 February-June; 5547 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Time Scale, Undated; 5548 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - University Press of America, 2004 August 31; 5549 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - University Press of America, 2007 June-July; 2912 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Subseries E: Technology and Society, 4391
    This subseries contains mostly correspondence and memoranda relating to the publication of Technology in Society, a journal founded and co-edited by George Bugliarello along with Polytechnic professor A. George Schillinger. Technology and Society is an international journal focused on the role of technology in society and its influence on economics, political and cultural dynamics.
    - 25th Anniversary Issue, 2004 April-August; 5504 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence – E-F, 1984-2001; 5506 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - G-H, 1984-1997; 5505 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence – O-P, 1985-1999; 5507 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence – Q-R, 1984-2002; 5508 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - Miscellaneous, 1998-2006, 1998 January - 2006 February; 5509 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - Miscellaneous, 2011, 2011 July 15; 5510 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Editorial, Acknowledgement, 1997 April 30; 5511 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Elsevier Science – Correspondence, 1995 February - 1996 June, 2002 July; 5515 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Elsevier Science - 2009-2010, 2009 October - 2010 February; 5512 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Elsevier Science Meeting, 2010 May-November; 5514 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Military Issue, 2000 August, 2001 February; 5516 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous - 2005 January, 5521 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous - 2008-2009, 5517 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous 2008-2010, 5518 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous - 2009-2010, 5519 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous - 2010 May-September, 5520 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous - 2010 May-November, 6323 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - New Journal, 2010 January - 2011 February; 5522 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Pergamon Press, Inc., 1986-1993; 5523 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Press Luncheon, 2004 May-July; 5524 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Proceedings, Ads, Publishers, 1985 November - 1987 September; 5525 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Barry Rosenblatt, 1992 January-November; 5526 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Harold P. Sjursen - Editor, 2010 March-September; 5527 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Special Issue – Volume 19, No. 2-3, 1997, 1996-1997; 5528 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Subseries F: Miscellaneous, 4243
    - "The 1983 DOE University Programs Panel Report: A University Perspective" - Forging New Engineering Partnerships Conference Proceedings – Midwest Universities Energy Consortium, 1993 November 4-5; 4280 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Articles - Miscellaneous - 1981-1997, 5557 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Articles and Speeches - Miscellaneous - 1985-1989, 5573 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Articles - Miscellaneous - 1987-1988, 5608 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Articles - Miscellaneous - 1990-1991, 5607 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Articles - Miscellaneous - 1997, 5609 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Articles - Miscellaneous - 2000-2001, 2000 February - 2001 October; 5561 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - "Bioengineering Ethics: Complexity and Synthesis" – International Journal of Medical Implants and Devices – Volume 1, No. 2, 2000; 4248 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - "Education for the Changing Pace of Technology: The Need to Transcend our Self-Imposed Boundaries" – Education for the Changing Pace of Technology – Volume 1, 1988; 4261 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - "Emerging and Future Areas of Engineering" – U.N.E.S.C.O. Report "Engineering Issues, Challenges and Opportunities for Development", 2010; 4253 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - "Engineering and Sustainable Development: Fostering Technology Innovation and Production" – U.N.E.S.C.O. Workshop on Science, Engineering and Industry: Innovation for Sustainable Development, 2011; 4250 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - "The Engineering Challenges of Urban Sustainability" – Journal of Urban Technology – Volume 15, No. 1, 2008 April; 4282 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - "Ethics of Medicine, Biology and Bioengineering at the New Critical Crossroads for our Species – Beyond Aristotle and Hippocrates" – Ethics in Biology, Engineering & Medicine – Volume 1, Issue 1, 2010; 4254 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - "Five Hundred Years Later" - American Scientist – Editorial, 1993; 5560 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - "Five Hundred Years Later" – American Scientist, Volume 81, 1993 March-April; 4251 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - "Generazione E Diffusione Delle INformazioni: Necessita Dei Paesi in Via Di Sviluppo" – Energia Ematerieprime, 1995 February; 5574 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - George Bugliarello's Handwritten Notes, 1975-1978; 5571 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - George Bugliarello's Handwritten Notes, Undated; 5572 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - "The History and Philosophy of Technology," Bugliarello, G. and D. Doner (Eds.) The History and Philosophy of Technology., 1979; 3737 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - "L'Importanza Delle Universita Americane Come Fonti Della Innovazione Tecnologica" - Federazione Nazionale Dirigenti Aziende Industriali, 1987; 4246 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - "Intellectual Property and Science Technology Policy for Participation in the Global Market" - Draft, 1997 December 18; 5558 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - "The Intelligent Layman's Guide to Technology" – Draft – Reprint, 1997; 5568 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Journal of Urban Technology – Richard E. Hanley, 2010-2011; 5579 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Journal of Urban Technology – Proofs, 2011 August-September; 5577 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Journal of Urban Technology – Urban Sustainability, 2011 May; 5578 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - "JUT Note: Technology and Bodegas" – Journal of Urban Technology – Volume 13, No. 2, 2006 August; 4283 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - "Megacities: Four Major Questions" – Journal of Urban Technology – Volume 16, No. 1, 2009 April; 4284 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - "Metrotech: Un parque urbano del conocimiento en New York" - Historia y Modernidad, 2003 December; 5580 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - "The New Engineering Education" - Engineering Education, 1973 February; 5567 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - "A New Trivium and Quadrivium" - American Scientist, 2002 September; 5566 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - "A Pivotal Resource at Risk" – American Scientist - Volume 80, No. 5, 1992 September-October; 4258 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - "Planning and Evaluating an Academic Merger and Making it Work" – Final Report to the Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1976 April 15; 5575 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Posthumous Publications, 2011; 5570 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - "Proceed with Caution" – American Scientis t – Volume 80, No. 6, 1992 November-December; 4256 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - "Reflections on Morality, Ethics and Bioethics Decisions" – Journal of Long-Term Effects of Medical Implants – Volume 18, Issue 1, 2008; 4249 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - "Reflections on Technological Literacy" – Bulletin of Science, Technology and Society – Volume 20, No. 2, 2000 April; 4260 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - "Reflections on Technological Literacy" - Drafts, 1999 September; 5565 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - "Restructuring Engineering Education: Disciplinary vs. Interdisciplinary" – New Challenges in Educating Engineers Conference, 1991 June 10-11; 4263 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - "Rethinking Research" – American Scientist – Volume 81, No. 1, 1993 January-February; 4257 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Science & Technology Book - Notes & Research, 1986-1999; 5585 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - "The Science-Technology-Society Matrix" – Bulletin of Science, Technology and Society – Volume 8, No. 2, 1988; 4255 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - "Six Figure Salaries for Engineering Professors" – American Society for Engineering Education – Proceedings of 1988 Annual Conference- University of Portland, 1988 June 19-23; 4252 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Slides, Undated; 4244 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - "Some Preliminary Thoughts on the City and the Brain", 2005 December - 2006 January; 5563 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Sustainable Development - Book Proposal, 2005 February 11; 5564 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - "Technology and Poverty", Undated; 5583 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - "Thirty Days Munition or: Technology and the Military Mind Set", Undated; 5584 (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - "Urban Sustainability: Science, Technology and Policies" – Journal of Urban Technology – Volume 11, No. 2, 2004 August; 4281 (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - "Verifiable Truths" – American Scientist, Volume 80, 1992 July-August; 4245 (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - "Why Study Science and Engineering at Private College" – Private College and Universities, 1989; 4259 (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - "Youth in Engineering and Sciences Program (YES)" – Education Partnerships for Work in the 21st Century: From Pilot to Policy: A Conference Report – N.Y.S. Legislative Commission on Science and Technology, 1989 March 31; 5576 (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - "The Super Collider: Key Policy Questions No One Is Asking", Undated; 5582 (Box 37, Folder 42)
- Series IV: Polytechnic, 4386
  This series contains documents pertaining to George Bugliarello's term as Chancellor (1994-2003) and President Emeritus (2003-2011) of Polytechnic and includes correspondence, memoranda, pamphlets, promotional material, and professional agendas and calendars documenting administrative functions, the development of the Center of Technology and Merchandising, the proposal for an Urban Sustainability Center, and the organization of the Leadership Seminar Series.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - Subseries A: Administrative Files, 4397
    - Jerry Hultin – Government Proposal, 2006 January; 5056 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Ilan Juran Class, RH 417, Undated; 5057 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Chemical Engineering Course – Sustainable Cities, CE 4043, Undated; 5058 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Sesquicentennial Convocation, 2005 September 29; 5059 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Sesquicentennial Celebration, 2003 September - 2005 October; 5060 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Strategic Planning, 2005 February-March; 5061 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Donald Othmer, 1971-1988; 5062 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Donald Othmer, 1989-1995; 5063 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Presidents' Circle, 2004 September-November; 5064 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Ilan Juran – Urban Infrastructure Institute, 2010 September; 5065 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Polytechnic University – Strategic Planning, 1989 October - 1992 October; 5066 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Chemical Engineering Department, 2004-2005; 5067 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Sabbatical Postponement, 2003 February-September; 5068 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - William Shore – Adjunct Professorship – RESTRICT, 2004 July-October; 5069 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Polytechnic University – Faculty Meeting, 2005 November 3; 5070 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Bugliarello's Academic, Development and Related Activities, 1998 April - 2002 June; 5071 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Faculty Professional Activities, 2005 June; 5072 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Ivan Frisch – Address to the Faculty, 2003 February 5; 5073 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Center for Technology in Supply Chains and Merchandising – Brochures & Prospectus, 2001 November-December; 5074 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Management of Technology and Innovation in Retailing (MOTIR), Undated; 5075 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - NYU Merger, 2007 September-October; 5076 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - George Schillinger Award, 2007 March-April; 5077 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Poly 100, 2007 March 19; 5078 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Chemical Engineering - CE 4043: Sustainable Cities – Course Outlines, 2010-2011; 5079 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Chemical Engineering - CE4043: Sustainable Cities – Course Outlines – Notes, Undated; 5080 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Chemical Engineering - CE 4053: City of the Future – Course Outlines, Undated; 5081 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Chemical Engineering - CE 4043: Sustainable Cities – Course Notes, Undated; 5082 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Chemical Engineering - CE 4043: Sustainable Cities – Course Notes, Undated; 5083 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - George Bugliarello Bio – Academic and Related Activities, 1994 June - 1998 March; 5084 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - "Planning and Evaluating an Academic Merger and Making it Work", 1976 April 15; 5085 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Civil Engineering - Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology Visit, 2004 September; 5086 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Othmer – Othmer Recognition Committee, 1998 September 30; 5088 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Othmer – Advisory Board, 2000 November; 5089 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Othmer – Othmer Institute Spring Event, 2003 October; 5090 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - Othmer – Donald Othmer Day, 1997 December 23; 5091 (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Othmer – Othmer Recognition Committee Meeting, 1998 July-August; 5092 (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Othmer – George Bugliarello Affidavit – RESTRICT, 1996 May 17; 5093 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - Othmer – "A Remembrance of Donald and Mildred Othmer", 2000 January 24; 5094 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Othmer – 1987 Mayor's Award for Science and Technology, 5095 (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - Othmer – Mrs. Mildred Topp Othmer, 1996 February 2; 5096 (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - Othmer – "Remembrance of Dr. Donald Othmer", 1995 December 4; 5097 (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - Othmer – N.A.E. Nomination, 1988; 5098 (Box 38, Folder 42)
    - Finances - Check Reimbursement – RESTRICT, 2010; 5099 (Box 38, Folder 43)
    - Presidential Candidates, 2005 April; 5721 (Box 38, Folder 44)
    - "A History of Aerospace Engineering at the Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn", Pasquale M. Sforza, Undated; 5100 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - "Drawing a Picture of our Future: Polytechnic University", 2005 September 9-10; 5101 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Polytechnic Preparatory Day School – Commencement Remarks, 1975 June 6; 5102 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - The Center for Regional Technology – Business / Labor Working Group, 1978 May 25; 5103 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Report of the Polytechnic Committee Prepared for the Polytechnic University Board of Trustees, 2005 January 25; 5104 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - "Towards the Technological University: The Story of Polytechnic Institute of New York" – Master, 1975 September 18; 5105 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Activity Report, 2006 September - 2009 September; 5106 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Strategic Planning 2000, 1998 August; 5107 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Polytechnic Fora, 2001 August, December; 5108 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Othmer Institute – Notes, 2001; 5109 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - C.T.F. - Miscellaneous, 1992-1994; 5110 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - C.T.F. - Miscellaneous, Undated; 5111 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Financial Engineering Institute, 1995 April - 1998 May; 5112 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - George Bugliarello's Academic and Related Activities, 1998-2001; 5113 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Othmer Institute for Interdisciplinary Studies at Polytechnic University, 2000 December; 5114 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Jerry Hultin, 2010 January 25; 5115 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - David Dibner Grant Proposal – Richard T. Sweeney, Vice Provost for Library & Information Services, 1994 May; 5116 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Board – Executive Committee, 1989 June - 1991 January; 5117 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Board of Trustees Statistics, 1998 March 5; 5118 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Collaboration with Unviersitia Delgi Studi Di Perugia, 1992 December; 5119 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Othmer Major Project Initiative, 2004 October - 2005 October; 5120 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Jerry Hultin – Ports, 2006 January-February; 5121 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Chemical Engineering – Course Evaluation Forms – RESTRICT, 2008 November; 5122 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Polytechnic Strategic Workshop, 2005 September 9-10; 5123 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - "University, Technology and the Community" – Outline, Undated; 5124 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - George Bugliarello Tribute, 1994; 5125 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Education Statistics, 1989-1992; 5126 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Visit of Australian Local Government and Public Works Engineering Delegation, 2009 September 18; 5127 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Graduate Center – "The Uses of Computers in High Schools", 1969 August; 5128 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Center for Technology in Merchandising, 2004 July; 5129 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Chemistry Department History, 2000 October - 2001 February; 5130 (Box 39, Folder 31)